<resources>
    <string name="app_name">bEtre</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="about_text">bEtre is a social media platform built for authentic self-expression. Inspired by the French word \"être\,\" meaning \"to be\,\" bEtre empowers users to share who they truly are.

    Our app allows users to create posts\, add location-based tags\, and engage in meaningful conversations. Whether you\'re connecting with friends or exploring new content\, bEtre helps you discover and express yourself in a genuine way.

    We believe in building a safe and respectful community. With tools for moderation and user management\, bEtre ensures a positive environment for everyone.

    At its heart\, bEtre is about being real\, being connected\, and being yourself.</string>

    <string name="contact_info">Contact us at: support@bEtre.com</string>

    <string name="privacy_info">
    Your privacy is important to us. We ensure that your data is protected and managed securely. Here are some key points about our privacy policy\: \n\n
    <br/><br/>
    &#8226; We do not share your personal information with third parties without your consent.\n
    &#8226; Your data is stored securely and is protected by encryption.\n
    &#8226; You can control see privacy settings and manage what information is shared.\n
    &#8226; We comply with all data protection regulations to ensure your information is safe.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="accounts_info">
    You have full control over your account settings and privacy preferences. Here are your rights and options for managing your account\:\n\n
    <br/><br/>
    &#8226; You can update your profile information\, including name\, phone\, and profile picture at any time.\n
    &#8226; Control your privacy by adjusting who can view your posts and profile.\n
    &#8226; You have the right to delete your account permanently, and all associated data will be removed.\n
    &#8226; Manage notifications to control what updates you receive from the app.\n
    &#8226; Review and update your security settings\, such as changing your password and enabling two\-factor authentication.\n
    </string>

</resources>